https://www.acebminc.com/terms-and-conditions.html

My Account
Orders
Comparison list
Track my order(s)
Track my order(s)
Sign inRegister
Email
PasswordForgot your password?
Checkout
Secure PayPal Checkout Without Account needed | Customer Service: 1-800-910-4223 or 1-818-548-7870
Home/Terms & Conditions
Product Categories..
Product Categories..
Comparison list
Track my order(s)
Track my order(s)
Sign inRegister
Email
PasswordForgot your password?
Register for a new account
Sign in
Remember me
Terms & Conditions
Order Cancellation Policy:
Cancel the order within 24 hours.
Once an order has been shipped, it can't be cancelled.
Special Order Items can't be cancelled once they have been placed with the supplier.
Prices:
Prices are subject to change without notice.
Order Fulfillment:
Orders are processed within 1-3 business day unless the product ordered is on backorder.
Back Orders:
Back order items will be automatically shipped when available. (Normally 4 – 6 business days)
Customer is responsible for shipping costs on returned merchandise.
Promotion may be modified or terminated at any time.
Excluding recondition and used units
Certain restrictions/destinations may apply.
In some cases overweight charges may apply.
We expect to offer this shipping special for a limited time, and may withdraw it any time at our discretion without providing advance notice.
Shipping Note: Shiping to Canada, Alaska, Hawaii is charge able.
Return Policy:
Please contact us to obtain a return authorization (RMA) number prior to return shipping an item.
Item Refund in 7 days: If the item you purchase doesn't meet or exceed your expectations, return in original condition within 7 days of purchase, and receive full purchase amount excluding shipping charge.
Within 7-30 days Items returned for mistaken purchases (e.g. changed mind, trial, miss-read the description, etc.) may incur a restocking fee up to 20% and shipping charge. For service related issues, all returns must have had a technical support phone consultation for the purpose of resolving any common configuration, initial setup and/or related issues.
Items returned poorly packaged (e.g. less than 4 inch packing material between internal product box and external shipping box), missing parts or accessories, or returned with wear or any damage caused by use or improper shipping may incur up to 20% restocking fee, plus any repair fee.
All our products will be insured for shipping.
No refund will be made for products that are used, or in a damaged condition. Merchandise must be returned in the same condition in which it was sent.
Shipping charges are not refundable. You will not receive credit for shipping and handling charges on returned merchandise. Customer is responsible for shipping and handling costs, as well as other applicable charges associated with the purchase or return of merchandise.
All approved returned products must be in the original box, well packaged, and should include all the items shipped with the product. You will be charged for missing items.
All returned products must accompanied by an RMA (Return Merchandise Authorization) number. An RMA number will be issued by Automatic bill countersat the time of return approval. Returns must be made within 10 daysfrom issuing RMA number.
All approved return items will be refunded back to you within 30 days of return, as per our guidelines.
Customers from Canada, Alaska, Hawaii, if you need to order products please contact customer service.
Privacy Policy:
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the ACE Business Machines website.
The only personal information we collect is your name, street and email address, telephone number.
We use the personal information collected from you to answer the email we receive, and process your order. Such personal information as we collect is not used for any other purpose and is not shared.
We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put into place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under the age of 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13 to provide information to us.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request detailing the error(s). To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
In the unlikely event any of the personal information you supply us online is misused, you may redress these issues by contacting us directly1-818-548-7870.
Share
Name of your friend
E-mail of your friend
Your name
Your e-mail
Your message
Terms & Conditions
Send
Tweet
Money Handling Equipment
Counterfeit Bill Scanner | Currency Discriminator Counter | Cash Counter Machines | mixed-money-counters | Amrotec X-1 | Amrotec X-Count | CD-1000 Currency Discriminator | Billcon D-551 |  AMROTEC X-1000 | Accubanker D-450 | Accubanker 1050 MG/UV | Carnation CR-180 | Money Counters | Accubanker AB-5500 | Magner 35-3 | Magner 75 | Magner 75M | Magner 75UM | Semacon S-1000 | Semacon S-1015 | Semacon S-1025 | Semacon S-1100 | Semacon S-1115 | Semacon S-1125 | Semacon S-1200 | Semacon S-1215 | Semacon S-1225 | Semacon S-1600 | Semacon S-1615 | Semacon S-1625 | Sercice Craden DP9 | Rent Currency Counters | Lease Money Counters
Customer Service
Customer Service
About us
Blog
Contact us
Privacy policy
Terms & Conditions
About your order
© 1997-2020 ACE Business Machines, Inc..
MY Account
MY Account
Orders
Comparison list
Track my order(s)
Track my order(s)
Sign inRegister
Email
PasswordForgot your password?
1545 N. Verdugo Rd. Suite 16 ; Gleandale, CA 91208 Tel: 1-818-548-7870 or 1-800-910-4223
Stay Connected
Enter your email address to receive special offers and promotions.
Email
Powered by Hungryweb.
